你是
我爸?
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
右翼
校对
Husky
特效
preisco
压制
♪ 嘿 邮递员先生 给我来份邮件♪
a♪ Hey, Mr. Postman, bring me a post ♪
♪ 给我那最爱的邮件♪
♪ Bring me the post that I love the most ♪
我勒个去
Dagnabit!
哟 包裹还没来吗?
Yo! No package yet?
包裹还没来
No package yet.
我确确实实在"高贵男孩"
I definitely ordered a pair of khakis
买了一条卡其裤
from The Distinguished Boy.
现在应该差不多送到了
They should've been delivered by now.
紫晶 我是个高贵的男孩
I'm a distinguished boy, Amethyst.
难道我配不上一条高贵的卡其裤吗
Don't I deserve distinguished khakis?
想来点儿这个吗?
Want one of these instead?
不了 谢谢
No, thanks.
它随时会到
Any second now.
嘿 邮递员先生 给我来份邮件
Hey, Mr. Postman, bring me a post!
真他喵的
Consarn it!
杰米还没来
Still no Jamie.
我不明白 他一直都很准时的
I don't understand. He's usually so punctual.
♪ 给我来份邮件
♪ Bring me a post
嘿 你不应该为了等什么邮件
Hey, you shouldn't have to waste your whole day
而浪费掉一整天
waiting for some thing in the mail.
把这罐魔法豆子带到市里
Take this can of magic beans into town
换一个甜甜圈来吧
and trade it for a donut!
你在喝…豆子?
You've been drinking... beans?
豆子对心脏有好处
They're good for the heart.
很遗憾 按照我的经验
Unfortunately, I know from experience
大甜甜圈是不接受魔法豆付款的
The Big Donut does not accept magic beans as currency.
但在我买甜甜圈的时候 你还会在这里等杰米的吧
But you'd still wait for Jamie while I got us some donuts?
当然 为什么不呢
Sure. Why not?
你不在的时候我们会坚守阵地的
We'll hold down the fort while you're gone.
紫晶 史蒂文
Amethyst! Steven!
看 我们在搭一座小房子--给螃蟹的房子!
Look! We're building a tiny house -- for crabs!
欢迎来到新家
Welcome to your new home.
噢 它们看起来很喜欢
Oh! They like it!
-谢啦 紫晶 -没关系
-Thanks, Amethyst! -No prob!
给我带个熊爪包回来就好
Just bring me back a bear claw!
早啊 酸奶油
Good morning, Sour Cream!
你今晚有锐舞表演吗?
Putting on a big rave tonight?
噢 你是说传单
Oh -- the fliers.
不 这些是关于洋葱头的
No, it's Onion.
走失
他已经失踪了好几天了
He's been missing for a couple of days now.
我妈和黄爹已经开始担心了
My mom and Yellowdad are starting to get worried.
你最近有见过他吗
You haven't seen him around lately, have you?
没有 你有去树林里他最喜欢的地方找过吗
No. Have you checked his favorite hiding spot in the woods?
当然了
Sure did.
那游乐场的自动售货机里呢
What about inside the vending machine at Funland?
没找到
No luck.
还费了我一块钱
Blew a dollar checking, too.
那你家里最机密的那个房间呢
What about that top-secret room inside your house?
你说他的办公室?  没有
You mean his office? Of course.
呃 我敢肯定他没事的
Eh, I'm sure he's fine.
如果他跟小时候的我一样
If he's anything like me when I was a kid,
他可能只是--我不确定--
he's probably just -- I don't know --
在一个朋友家后院锐舞
raving in a friend's backyard.
不管怎么说 我最好把剩下这些贴起来
Anyway, I'd better hang the rest of these up.
你能给拉尔斯和莎蒂一张吗
Can you make sure Lars and Sadie get one of these?
我想在大甜甜圈也贴一张
I wanted to hang one up at The Big Donut,
不过它关门了
but it's closed.
关门了
Closed?
拉尔斯
Lars!
莎蒂噫噫噫噫噫
Sadieeeeeee!
他们肯定在这儿
They have to be here.
我知道你们在干什么
I know what you guys are doing.
你们在休息室看恐怖电影
You guys are watching scary movies in the break room,
正如你们不该做的那样
like you're not supposed to be!
开门啊
Open up!
我想要个甜甜圈
I...want...a donut!
嘿 你是想破门而入还是怎样
Hey! You trying to break in or something?
巴布!  呃 不是
Barb! Uh...no.
我 我只是在找拉尔斯和莎蒂
I-I was just looking for Lars and Sadie.
但他们不在这里
But they're not back here.
呃 你是怎么进去的
Uh... how did you get in?
作为一个好母亲 怎么说也得
Well, what kind of mother would I be
有自己女儿所有钥匙的备份啊
if I didn't make a copy of all my daughter's keys?!
我只是过来送莎蒂的午餐
I only came over to drop off Sadie's lunch.
她昨晚不在家 所以我想我应该送到这儿
She wasn't home last night, so I figured I'd bring it here.
但这地方连人影都没
But the place was completely empty.
也许今天是什么面包师节之类的
Maybe it's some sort of baker's holiday.
肯定不是个国家节日
It's certainly not a federal one.
莎蒂昨晚没回家?
Sadie never came home last night?
嘛 她也算一个成人了
Eh, she's an adult.
可能只是溜出去跟她男朋友
Probably just snuck off
再来个岛屿探险之旅
for another "island adventure" with her boyfriend.
那不可能
That couldn't be.
他们当时是要去聚会的
They were going to go to a party together,
但是拉尔斯一直没来
but Lars never showed.
我们离开时 莎蒂说她要回家
And when me and Sadie left, she said she was going home.
而现在 酸奶油正到处寻找洋葱头
And now Sour Cream is looking everywhere for Onion.
我正在等杰米的一个包裹
And I was expecting a package today from Jamie,
但他--他一直没送来
but he -- he never delivered it.
一个包裹
A package?
你是说一个大概这么大 两磅 也许四盎司的包裹吗
You mean one about yea big, 2 pounds, maybe 4 ounces?
我高贵的卡其裤!
My distinguished khakis!
那你看到杰米了吗?
Did you see Jamie with them?
今天早上看到了--
I did this morning --
就在我派他去你那里之前
just before sending him off to your place.
巴布 形势也许非常严峻
Barb, this might be serious.
我去看看能不能在木板道那里找到什么人
I'll go see if I can find anyone on the boardwalk.
我到每家门前去找找堆积着的包裹
I'll go check doorsteps for piled-up packages.
这样我们就知道还有谁失踪了
Then we'll know if anyone else is missing.
莎蒂 别怕 亲爱的
Sadie! Don't worry, honey!
妈妈来了 宝贝女儿
Mama's comin' for ya, baby girl!
祝好运
Good luck.
杰米
Jamie...
洋葱头
Onion...
拉尔斯
Lars...
莎蒂
Sadie?
也许他们都去度假了
Maybe they're all on vacation?
不 史蒂文
No, Steven.
无论是发生了什么 我都应该找到他们
Whatever the case, it's up to me to find them.
杰米 洋葱头
Jamie! Onion!
拉尔斯 莎蒂
Lars! Sadie!
-正在等待肯定我的挑战者
Awaiting new challengers to validate me.
-来个人胖揍我一顿吧 拜托了
Somebody, punch me! Please.
嘛 酸奶油说的没错
Well, Sour Cream was right --
洋葱头不在自动售货机里
Onion wasn't in the vending machine.
其他人也不在
And neither was anybody else.
你是我爸爸吗
Are you my dad?
啊啊啊 一个宝石人
Aaah! A Gem!
你是我爸爸吗
Are you my dad?
我得找到我爸爸
I need to find my dad.
不不 我不是
N-No, I-I'm not.
等等等一下
W-W-Wait! Wait!
别又让我陷入一个谜啊
Don't leave me with another enigma!
她的本体在她眼睛下方
And the gem was under her eye --
我们的左手边 她的右手边
our right, her left.
还有翅膀…没错
And the wings and...yeah.
我想我把一个眼睛画大了
I think I made one eye bigger than the other.
我是跟着感觉走的
I was going for a feeling.
说真的我连个圆都画不好
Honestly, I can't even draw a circle.
好吧 石榴 你只是画了你自己
Okay, Garnet, you just drew yourself.
呃 我喜欢我自己
Uh, I like me.
好吧 我想康妮是画的最像的
Well, anyway, I think Connie was the closest.
谢谢
Thanks!
这真是浪费时间
This was a waste of time.
我们应该准备战斗
We should be preparing for a fight!
不管她是谁 她都是来自母星的
Whoever this is, she's from Homeworld.
她一定是来找我们的
She's got to be here for us!
其实并不是 她说她是来找她爸爸的
She's not, though. She said she's looking for her dad.
啥 她爸?
What? Her dad?
这么多人都失踪了
There are all these people missing.
说不定她爸也失踪了
Maybe her dad's gone missing, too.
但是宝石人没有爹啊
But Gems don't have dads!
这不合理
This doesn't make any sense.
史蒂文就是个宝石人 他也有个爹
Steven's a Gem, and Steven has a dad.
但是没有其他像史蒂文这样的宝石人了
There are no other Gems like Steven.
你确定
Are you sure?
我们必须一探究竟
We've got to get to the bottom of this.
我们应该分开行动
We should split up and investigate.
红宝石和蓝宝石
Ruby and Sapphire!
呃 不是 我是说分成小队
Uh, no. I meant split into teams.
哦对
Oh. Right.
石榴你自己一队 珍珠和紫晶 康妮和我一队
Garnet with yourself, Pearl with Amethyst, and Connie with me.
出发
Let's go!
康妮 你真的认为
Connie, do you really think
还可能有我这样的宝石人吗
there could be another Gem like me?
嘛 你懂宝石人懂得比我多
Well, you know more about Gems than I do.
但没什么不可能 你就存在啊
But it can't be impossible. You exist.
但她看起来没有人类血统
She didn't look half human, though.
她的皮肤是蓝色的…还有翅膀
She was blue and...had wings.
也许她是被收养的
Well, what if she's adopted?
也许她坠入一个大城市
What if she crash-landed in the big city
也许她被一个拥有金子般的心的
and she was taken in by a lonely millionaire
孤独的富翁收养了
with a heart of gold?
还拥有万贯家产
And a house of gold.
但是有一天他去沙滩市出差
But one day, he went on a business trip to Beach City
却再也没回来
and he never came home.
这故事拍成电影我肯定会看的
I guess I'd watch the movie of that.
或者写成书
Or read the book.
或者两者皆非 因为它可能是真事儿 史蒂文
Or neither, 'cause it could be reality, Steven!
你真的这么认为
You really think so?
嘿 只有找到真相我们才能知道
Hey, the only way to know is to find out.
对
Yeah!
嗯 这儿有风
Yup. There's wind.
天啊
Man.
我记得在这里和洋葱头他们玩
I feel like I was just here
感觉就像昨天发生的事
with Onion and all his friends.
他到底去哪了
Where is he?
可怜的酸奶油 丢了他的弟弟
Poor Sour Cream, missing his brother...
巴布丢了她女儿
and Barb missing her daughter --
和她的邮差--
and her mailman --
还有这个宝石人丢了她的爸爸!
and this new Gem missing her dad!
我能理解一个人失去老爸的滋味
I know what it's like to have your dad taken away.
她一定害怕极了
She must be so scared.
但你成功找回了你爸
But you got your dad back.
你也一定能帮她找到
And you'll solve this, too.
我们会一起找到
We'll solve this -- together.
谢谢 康妮
Thanks, Connie.
好 让我们把这片树林翻个底朝天吧
Okay. Let's turn these woods upside down.
洋葱头
Onion!
拉尔斯
Lars!
杰米
Jamie!
你在这儿给苔藓送包裹吗?
You in here delivering packages to some peat moss?
史蒂文 是那个宝石人
Steven! It's the Gem!
什么
What?
她看起来和我画的一模一样
She looks just like my drawing!
过来这里 别怕 我们会帮你的
Come on. You don't have to be afraid. We'll help you!
跳进我怀里
Jump down into my arms.
我会接住你的
My body will break your fall.
你是我爸爸吗
Are you my dad?
啥
What?
不 我 我不是你爸
No. I-I'm not your dad.
但我们可以帮你找到你爸
We can help you find your dad.
我不是在找你爸
I'm not looking for your dad.
我在找我爸爸
I'm looking for my dad.
我得找到我爸爸
I need to find my dad.
好吧
Right.
我们…会帮你
Well, we'll...help you.
康妮
Connie!
康妮 等等 小心啊
Connie, wait! Be careful!
康妮 你是康妮吗
Connie. Are you Connie?
对 我是康妮
Yes! I'm Connie!
我是--康妮 康妮是--朋友
Me -- Connie. Connie -- friend.
托帕石
Topaz!
我找到了一个 我找到了一个
I found one! I found one!
我找到了一个康妮
I found a Connie!
史蒂文
Steven?
康妮
Connie!
还有一个宝石人
Another Gem!
她 她劫持了所有人
She -- She has everyone!
放开他们
Let them go!
康妮
Connie!
看着这些有机体蠕动的样子
Look at those organics squirming around.
把我的朋友还给我
Give me back my friends!
别费神听那个史蒂文了
Don't bother listening to that Steven.
他不是我爸爸
He's not my dad.
现在我们只需要我爸爸 然后我们就走
Now all we need is my dad, and we're out of here!
她们居然派一个海蓝宝
Can't believe they wasted an Aquamarine
浪费时间做这种任务
on a job like this.
这太简单了 你都可以一个人完成了 托帕石
It's so easy, you could have done it yourself, Topaz.
不
No.
你不可以带走他们
You can't take them.